谢谢各位这么晚还能留下来
Thank you, everyone, for staying late
学习我们新的平板电脑点餐系统
to learn our new iPad order system.
我们还能怎么着 你从外面把门给锁了
We had no choice, you locked the door from the outside.
怎么都好 咱们都要学
Either way, we're learning.
Han 为啥要升级咱们的点菜系统啊
Han, why would we update our order system
我们穿着七十年代的制服
when our uniforms are from the 1970's
拿的薪水是十九世纪的水平?
and our paycheck is from the 1800s?
我们开始教程吧
Let's get to the tutorial.
Max 你和我进行角色扮演
Max, you and I are going to role-play.
好啊 你来扮小婊子
All right, you can be the little bitch,
我就扮我自己
and I'll be me.
我不需要上这堂课
I don't need this lesson.
我很熟悉触屏
I'm very familiar with the touch screen.
谷歌的"谷"字就是我写上去的
Let's just say I put the "goo" in Google.
我来扮演顾客
I'm going to pretend I'm a customer,
要点一个汉堡
and order a hamburger.
你好 小姐 我要一个汉堡
Hello, miss. I'll have a hamburger.
当然可以 小姐
Certainly, miss.
请问您要不要加一点沙门氏菌?
Would you like that with or without salmonella?
Han 史蒂夫.乔布斯给我上了第一堂平台电脑课
Han, I got my first lesson on the iPad from Steve Jobs,
现在我还得让韩.乔布斯教我?
and now I'm getting it from Han Jobs?
Caroline 别表现得像是你比我懂这些玩意儿
Caroline, don't act like you know more about gadgets than me.
曾经的富人可比不过现在的亚洲人
Formerly rich doesn't beat currently Asian.
现在 大家看着自己的平板电脑
Now, come on, everyone look at their iPads.
什么平板电脑? 我没看到平板电脑
What iPad? I didn't see an iPad
什么? 不
What? No.
刚刚有人说平板电脑了吗?
Did somebody say something about an iPad?
啥是平板电脑啊?
What the hell is an iPad?
平板电脑都跑哪去了?
Where did they all go?
我猜是到淘宝上去了
I'm guessing eBay.
都给我拿回来 尤其是我那部
I want them all back, especially mine.
我在和一个在澳大利亚的女人调情呢
I'm in a casual flirtation with a woman in Australia.
她有一半的土著人血统 但她性格很好
She's part aboriginal, but has a great personality.
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 。沫
时间轴: 。沫
翻译: Astral  波特妹子  落寞卷菜
校对: 桃茜茜
给你 Earl
Here you go, Earl.
Max 出什么事了? 你看上去很开心
Max, what's wrong? You seem happy.
我还在为上周拿到的一万块钱贷款
I'm just still on a high from this $10,000 bank loan
而感到飘飘然
I got last week.
还有就是因为我在2004年吃的那个有大麻的蛋糕
And from an almost certainly laced pot brownie I ate in 2004.
我真不敢相信你和Caroline没有劫持人质
I can't believe you and Caroline got a bank loan
就能为你们的纸杯蛋糕生意
for your cupcake business,
争取到银行贷款
and not a single hostage was involved.
Max 这一万美元可不是你的
Max, you don't have $10,000.
你甚至连在线影视都看不起
You don't even have Netflix.
这钱是来生产咱们纸杯蛋糕衣服的
This money is to pay a factory to make our cupcake T-shirts,
我已经把范围缩小到三家了
and I've whittled it down to three.
你好
Hello.
说到缩小
Speaking of whittled.
有人用了我的打印机 我猜是Caroline
Someone used my printer, and I'm guessing it's Caroline,
因为这是关于商业的
'cause it's about business
而不是Earl的安吉拉・贝塞特的拼接画
and not another one of Earl's Angela Bassett collages.
兄弟 我能说什么呢? 我就是个贝塞特迷
What can I say, man? I'm a Bassett hound.
哦 谢谢 Han
Oh, thanks, Han.
这些是我正在调查的几家工厂
These are the factories I've been researching.
我们希望我们的T恤衫是美国货
We want our T-shirts to be American made.
我有个女佣也是个美国货
I have an American maid,
而她只会吃我的燕麦卷
and all she's good at is eating my granola bars.
你看 Max 我在布鲁克林这里找到了一家
Look, Max, I found one right here in Brooklyn.
"美国Ace公司 创始人Ace Hardwick
"American Ace. The founder, Ace Hardwick,
致力于优待他的工人们
is devoted to treating his workers well,"
而不是像AA服饰老板那样变态
and not in a creepy way like that American Apparel guy.
你是说在那些工人里
So you're saying none of these workers
没有人被他们的老板插过吗?
have ever found an Ace in their hole?
听着 我在很多工厂里工作过
Look, I've worked in a lot of factories.
我知道这是怎么回事
I know what goes on.
我在一个做大衣的服装厂里干过活
I worked in a coat factory,
所以我的肺上才裹了一层石棉
which is why my lungs are coated in asbestos.
我在一个做内裤的服装厂里干过活
I worked in an underwear factory,
工资还低得要死
where I was underpaid for the fruits of my looms,
最糟糕的就是奶酪蛋糕工厂
and worst factory of all, The Cheesecake Factory.
哦
Oh.
我们要不明天再看一下
How about we do a walk-through tomorrow
保证一切正常?
to make sure it's up to snuff?
要是有啥能让我正常的
Well, if they have snuff,
那咱们为啥还要等到明天啊?
why are we waiting till tomorrow?
嘿 大家好!
Hey, everybody!
哦 嘿 嗨 我有大好消息!
Oh, hey. Hi, great news!
我刚在布法罗鸡翅烧烤吧点酒被查身份证了!
I just got carded at Buffalo Wild Wings!
真的吗? 我有一次还从里面被赶出来了呢
Really? I got carted out of there once.
我还有好消息
And more great news:
我也要开始我自己的新生意了
I'm starting my own new business.
妹子们 你们现在手头上有一万块对吧?
So girls, you know how you have that $10,000?
呃 我不想把你们的钱都掏空
Well, I don't want to clean you out,
要不你们就给我个9500块吧?
but how do you feel about tossing me $9,500?
你们两个应该投资 Sophie的生意真是绝妙
You two should invest. Sophie's business is genius.
你知道有很多女孩把她们下面的阴毛
You know how a bunch of ladies got their down-there-hair
都永久剃掉了吗?
permanently lasered off?
没错 就是把你的下面清理得锃亮
Yeah, that's when your waxer gives you a Michael Chiklis.
是啊
Yeah.
Sophie有一个产品
Well, Sophie's offering a product
可以让你的杂草丛再长回去
that puts grass back on your field.
对的
Yeah.
那才不是什么生意 没人会要这个的
That's not a business. That's nobody's business.
我才不做那种事
Yeah, I don't do any of that stuff.
我随便在那地方丢一撮毛就可以了
I just throw a scrunchie on mine and go.
嘿 这会有市场需求的 有时在迷雾中
Hey, there's a need for this. Sometimes, in the fog,
没有起落跑道 我的飞机会迷路的
my plane gets lost without a landing strip.
我们不加入了
We're out.
哦 女孩们 先别决定
Oh, don't decide yet, girls.
你们还没听到它可爱的名字呢
you haven't even heard the cute, little name.
"苏菲库金斯基的阴道假发"
"Sophie Kuchenksi's Vagina Wigs!"
我们真的不加入了
Yeah, we're really out.
哦 但这绝对是个高质量的产品
Oh. But it's a quality product,
这还是中国进口的真阴毛呢
and it's real hair imported from "Va-China."
我们真的真的不会投资了
Yeah, never been further out.
这是我们的主楼层
And this is our main floor.
哇 这太棒了!
Wow, this is amazing!
我感觉我们是进了巧克力工厂
I feel like we're in the Willy Wonka Factory.
是啊 对吧?
I know, right?
美国王牌工厂的座右铭是"劳动最快乐"
The American Ace motto is "work is fun""
Max以为这工厂是另一种样子的
Max was expecting a different kind of factory.
多一点折磨 少一点桌上足球
More torture, less foosball.
是啊 对吧? 在American Ace就不会那样
I know, right? Not at American Ace.
你在这里的职位是什么 Peggy?
And what is your position here, Peggy?
你是个只会说"是啊 对吧"的人吗
Are you the "I know, right?" person?
是啊 对吧?
I know, right?
不 我也是这工厂的合伙人 我还负责给T恤衫染色
No, I'm one of the owners. Also, I dye T-shirts.
所有员工在这里工作半年后都能拿到股份
See, every employee gets a percentage of the company
所以你呆的时间越久 你的股份就会增长
after six months, so the longer you stay, the more it grows.
我们在餐馆已经工作四年了
We've been at the diner four years,
我们只看到Oleg裤子里那个东西增长过
and the only thing we've seen grow is Oleg's pants.
是啊 对吧?
I know, right?
呃 Ace等着你们呢 去吧 玩得开心!
Well, Ace is expecting you. Go ahead, go have fun!
嘿 不要被表象迷惑了
Hey, don't be fooled by what's on the surface.
你看上去好像很有钱
You look like you have money,
但我知道你的内裤已经碎成多条布
but I know your underwear's in shreds.
才不是多条 就一条
Not shreds, Max, shred.
只剩一条 从前拉到后面
Just one, it goes from front to back.
嗯 嗨 我们能进来吗? 门开着
Um, hi, should we just come in? The door is open.
是的 门一直都开着
Yep, always is.
门会设限 设限可不好
Doors create boundaries. Boundaries are a bummer.
你知道还有什么事很不好吗?
You know what else is a bummer?
人很高但鸡巴很小?
Tall guys with small penises?
你们刚好错过了高档意大利雪糕以及咖啡车
That you just missed the gelato and designer coffee cart.
要来个特浓咖啡榛子果仁糖味吗?
Espresso hazelnut praline?
我们不是来吃雪糕的
We're not here for gelato.
我们可不是不来吃雪糕的
We're not not here for gelato.
太棒了 见到你真棒
Awesome. It's awesome to meet you.
我是Ace Hardwick
I'm Ace Hardwick.
听着 Ace 我们才不会给你一万美金
Look, "Ace", we're not about to give you $10,000
好让你却说装货码头旁 占那些悲伤的
so you can take advantage of a sad, underage girl worker
未成年女员工的便宜 就因为她胸超大
near the loading docks 'cause her boobs are crazy big
然后她还得自行搭车回家
and she needs a ride home.
我就"举个例子"
That's a "for instance."
你在说什么?
I'm sorry?
是这样的Ace 一涉及到工厂
See, Ace, Max has some trust issues
Max她就诸多怀疑 我们今天来这儿是...
when it comes to factories, so, we're here today to...
你现在基本上是在啃盒子了
You're pretty much eating cardboard there.
想再来个吗?
You want me to get you another?
你还没见过她吃金枪鱼罐头的样儿呢
You should see her with tuna cans.
嘿 我看到了意大利熏火腿肠
Hey, I see the prosciutto cart.
谁想吃进口火腿?
Who wants imported ham?
我!
Me!
好吧 我们不是来这里啃火腿肠的
Well, we're not not here for prosciutto.
你知道什么很厉害吗?
Hey, you know what's cool?
人矮器大的?
Short guys with big penises?
你很有趣
You're fun.
你们的生意就该给美国王牌工厂
Your business belongs here at American Ace.
来 去认识一下家庭成员
Come on, let's go meet the family.
这个家伙有点吓人啊
That guy kind of creeps me out.
但往好处想 我终于能见家人了
On the plus side, I finally get to meet my family.
这个地方是我专门用来提供正能量
I had this space designed for open energy
和自由谈话的
and open conversation.
你们好吗 合伙人们?
What's up, other owners?
你好啊 Ace
What's up, Ace?
我们的销量 上升了四倍!
Our sales, by 400%!
Max 就这么定了 就是这家工厂
Max, this is it. This is our factory.
员工们看起来都很开心有成就感
The employees look happy and successful.
超级男孩的队员以前也是啊(美国歌手组合)
So did the members of 'N Sync.
但到了幕后 全是一把鼻涕一把泪
but behind the curtain, a veil of tears.
嘿 Caroline 意大利熏火腿在这儿
Hey, Caroline, here's the prosciutto cart.
谢谢你 Ace!
Thanks, Ace!
慢用 我要来个
Enjoy. I'm just gonna get
五分钟的椅子按摩
a quick five-minute chair massage.
快 趁Ace把脑袋塞到椅子屁股里之时
Come on, let's slip out while Ace has got his head
我们赶紧走
stuck in that chair's ass.
嘿 你好啊?
Hey, what's up?
欢迎来到美国王牌 我是Rico
Welcome to American Ace. I'm Rico.
你真是 太太太漂亮了
You're, like, really, really, really pretty.
啊... 哦!
Aw... oh!
总之 我是合伙人之一 负责清洗厕所
So anyways, I'm part owner, and I clean the bathroom.
小问题: 你们有醇香的解百纳吗?
Hmm, quick question: do you have a light Cabernet?
小小问题:
Quicker question:
你们虐待童工的密室在哪里?
where's the secret room with the toddler slaves?
你好 我叫Raul 合伙人兼保安
What's up? I'm Raul, part owner and security guard.
你们想抽空喝一杯么?
Hey, you two want to grab a drink sometime?
周五下班后 我们都在旁边的玉米饼店放松
Fridays after work, we all hang next door at Tortilla Flats.
玉米饼店 这不是你当脱衣舞娘的艺名吗?
Tortilla Flat. Wasn't that your stripper name?
你这是嫉妒我的约会对象长得高
You're just jealous 'cause mine's taller
而且觉得我非非非常漂亮
and thinks I'm really, really, really pretty.
祝你找到个高器不小的
Good luck with that tall guy scenario.
抱歉迟到了 我们在忙别的事呢
Sorry we're late, but we were busy with our other business,
我们真正在乎的事
the one we care about.
我怎能不接受你们"诚心诚意"的道歉呢?
How can I be mad with that sincere, heartfelt apology?
谁想看看我们TS样本？
Who wants to see our sample T-shirts?
我想看 但我还想看很多东西
I want to see it, but I want to see a lot of things.
可是由于白内障 我只能是
With these damn cataracts, the best I can do
两眼一眯看个轮廓了
is look towards it and get a milky idea.
嘿 姑娘们!
Hey, girls!
我想给你们看"周末假阴毛大放送"
I want to show you some of my new styles
收集的一些新设计
for my "Everybody's Merkin for the Weekend" collection.
Sophie 什么是假阴毛?
Sophie, what's a merkin?
就是阴道假发
It's a vagina wig.
哦 好下流
Oh, that's dirty.
Han 我需要你的建议
And Han, I'm gonna need your input,
因为我正开发亚洲系列产品
because I'm working on an Asian line.
Han在乱给建议之前
Shouldn't Han grow some hair on his
不应该先自己长点毛吗?
before he starts tossing out advice?
Han 我想知道毛的质感对不对
Han, I need to know if I got the texture right,
所以给我过来
so come over here.
哦 没错
Oh, yeah.
啊 摸起来好极了 哦
Yeah, that feels nice. Ohh.
哦
Ohh.
在我指间柔顺又茂密
Yeah, nice and thick between my fingers.
就是这个感觉
Oh, yeah.
慢点
Slower.
再慢点
Slower still.
这就像是在看你的沙鼠蹂躏铅笔
This is like watching your gerbil hump a pencil.
虽然没啥少儿不宜的 但真让人恶心
Not really sexual, but still grosses you out.
Sophie 我... 我觉得你该停手了
Sophie, I... I think you should stop.
自从三年级的易老师给我检查头虱以后
I haven't felt this sensation since third grade
我再也没有这种感觉了
when Madam Yi checked me for head lice.
记得提醒我明天给Han买那本
Remind me to pick up a "What's Happening To My Body?"
"写给青春期女孩"的书
book for Han tomorrow.
姑娘们 我就坐在这边
Oh, girls, I'll be over here,
研究我的非裔美国人系列产品
working on my African/American line.
我很纠结该叫"非草集"
Yeah, I can't decide whether to call it a "vag-afr""
还是"北美第二春"
or a "Pube-a Gooding, Jr""
Max 快看 这些衬衫太漂亮了
Max, look. These shirts look amazing.
看来我看错那家工厂了
Well, I guess I was wrong about the factory.
就像我误以为
Like I was wrong about you
你活不过第一个冬天
making it through that first winter.
快看 里面有张纸条
Look, there's a note in here.
哦 可能是Rico写的 他迷上我了
Oh, it's probably from Rico. He's obsessed with me.
呃 不是他
Yeah, it's not from him.
上面写着 "救救我们"
It says, "Help us""
低薪员工被困工厂求救 我就知道是这样!
Underpaid workers are trapped in that factory, I knew it!
我又被冰淇淋蒙蔽了双眼
Once again, I was fooled by ice cream.
没错 纸条上写着 "救救我们"
Yes, it's a note that says, "Help us,"
但是我在商科学校学到一个道理
but if there's one thing I learned in business school,
那就是 眼不见便不存在
it's if you don't see it, it doesn't exist.
虽然我们不想多事 但我们不能视而不见
Look, as much as we want to, we can't just look away.
我们要去找那些工人谈谈
We need to talk to the workers.
给那个认为你很漂亮的家伙打电话
Call the guy, the one who thinks you're pretty.
我不知道你说的是谁
I don't know who you're talking about.
我只认识一个家伙
I only met a guy who thought
他认为我很很很漂亮
I was really, really, really pretty.
我们可以在墨西哥餐厅见他们
We can meet them at that Mexican place.
噢 墨西哥餐厅
Ooh, a Mexican place!
我把拉丁美洲的市场给忘了!
I forgot about the Latina market!
妹子们 你们去到那里的时候记得看看
Girls, when you're there, find out if they'd be interested
他们是否对国界以南的毛发感兴趣
in some hair south of the border.
不知道你们是否想喝啤酒或者是玛格利塔
Didn't know if you ladies wanted beers or margaritas,
所以我们给你们拿了啤格利塔
so we got you Beer-garitas.
这要五美元呢 但你们值这个价
It's five bucks, but you're worth it.
我爱死了好食欲的妹子
I love a girl with a healthy appetite.
好吧 看来在我把开胃菜吃完之前
Well, you're gonna be getting down on one knee
你就要单膝跪地了
before the end of the appetizers.
咱们就开门见山吧 工厂待你们好吗?
So let's just dive right in. How's factory life treating you?
给咱们来点内部情报... 当你们拿来这些
Give us the skinny... which is what I hope you said
啤格利塔时 我就想听你们说说了
when you ordered those Beer-garitas,
因为我的腰部赘肉还在
'cause I cannot be poor with a muffin top.
我不想谈论工作
You know, I don't want to talk about work.
你是说你们不允许谈论工作?
Oh, are you saying you're not allowed to talk about work?
你的话我们都听到了 Rico还是Raul来着
Your words, we all heard you, Rico or Raul.
嘿 告诉我 你们女孩子喜欢干点啥?
Hey, tell me, what do you girls like to do?
我喜欢服务员在我的桌前制作鳄梨色拉酱
Mm, I like to watch waiters make guacamole at my table.
那是啥时候的事?
When's that gonna happen?
那么你们的工作... 好吧
So about work... Yeah, okay.
嘿 让我们瞧瞧啤格利塔有啥好的
Hey, let's go see what's going on in Beer-garitaville.
我们要怎么做? 我从Rico嘴里
What are we gonna do? I can't get any information
套不出情报 他实在是太着迷于
out of Rico. He's so preoccupied
这个很很很漂亮的我了
with how pretty, pretty, pretty I am.
嗨 Peggy 你们好吗
Oh, hi, Peggy. How are you?
你们想要和我们一起聊聊工作吗
Would you like to join us and talk about work?
不如咱们来谈谈你们两个
Why don't we talk about you two skanks
讨人厌的家伙赶紧滚蛋吧?
gettin' the hell outta here?
我还以为我们俩才是坏服务员
And I thought we were bad waitresses.
这个是Carmen 她也在厂里工作
This is Carmen. She works at the factory too.
我们是死党 然后她也是股东 和我一样
We're BFFs, and she's one of the owners, like me.
没错 Rico从头到脚都是她的 所以别打歪主意
Yeah, and she's a 100% owner of Rico, so hands off.
你们俩坐在这儿
We seen you two sittin' over here
自以为是他妈的上帝的宠儿
like you're God's friggin' gift.
我就知道 不是吗? 而且
I know, right? And not for nothing,
Rico的"好狗"可不喜欢别的女人
but Rico's pit bull doesn't like other girls.
我猜 那就是他的"好狗"
I'm guessing that's his pit bull.
还有你 别打Raul的主意
And you, hands off Raul.
我们的爱情是深厚真挚的
We have a love that is deep and real,
当他发现之时 就将会成就奇迹
and when he finds out about it, it's gonna be magic.
果然... 不出我所料
Yup... Exactly what I expected.
楼上是巧克力工厂
Upstairs is Willy Wonka's factory,
可是楼下却是人间炼狱
and down here, they're waterboarding Oompa Loompas.
嘿 有事吗? 我们跟平常一样
Yo, what's up? We just comin' here to work
来染料厂上班
in the dye room right there as per usual.
耶 没什么大不了的 有什么好看的?
Yeah, no biggie. What yous twos lookin' at?
口音学得挺像啊
That was a really good accent.
谢谢 我可是在"油脂"里演过Rizzo
Thanks. I played Rizzo in Grease.
本来应该演Sandy
Should have been Sandy, but I let
但是我让另一个跛脚的女孩演了
the girl with the limp have it.
快点 我们得穿上这个进染坊
Come on, we have to put these on and go into the dye room,
我觉得那里有着不可告人的秘密
cause I'm guessing that's where it all goes down.
染坊 不出我所料
The dye room, I'm not surprised.
我一直都觉得我们会混到一块儿
I always knew we'd dye together.
好的 我们就假装是在这里打工
Okay, we'll just pretend to be working here,
像我们在餐厅做的那样
like we do at the diner.
哇奥 看看谁来了
Well, well, look who it is,
傲慢鬼一号和傲慢鬼二号 英雄荣归
Stuck-Up and Stuck-Up Two: The Legend Returns.
Max 咱们撤吧 我不能穿着灰色赴死
Max, we gotta go. My life can't end wearing grey.
什么事 小妞?
What up, ladies?
昨晚 你们还跟小白脸出去鬼混
Last night, you're hanging with the homies,
但是今天 嘭 你们也到这儿来上班了
and today, boom, you just happen to be working here.
可真是报应啊
That's friggin' convenient.
我就知道 不是吗?
I know, right?
活该
Very friggin' convenient.
我就知道 不是吗?
I know, right?
我们得让她们知道谁才是老大
We just have to show them who's boss.
就像我们对待吐司机里的
You know, like we do with the mouse
的老鼠那样
who lives in our toaster.
那我们该怎么办 尖叫着用清洁剂喷他们?
So, what, we're gonna scream and then spray Windex at them?
嘿! 看见这个疤了吗?
Yo! See this scar?
为了一份冰沙 于是和五个天主教的女生挥刀打架
Knife fight with five Catholic schoolgirls
所以 除非你想跟甲乙丙丁这四人
over a slushie. So unless you want
以及那个最后坐轮椅的女生一样
some of what I gave Virginia, Stephanie, Laquetia, Latoya,
不然就放聪明点
and the one in the wheelchair, I'd stay clear.
这只是一个误会
This is just a misunderstanding.
Rico对我没兴趣
Rico's not interested in me.
是吗 好像他昨晚对你很有兴趣吧
Well, he seemed pretty into you last night.
呃 没错 但那是在她开口讲话之前
Huh, yeah, but that's before she talked.
别这样啦 我们根本对你们的男人没兴趣
Come on, we are not interested in your men at all.
绝对没有 我是说 这怎么可能嘛
Not at all. I mean, come on.
什么意思?
What's that mean?
你是说 他们不够好?
You're saying something's wrong with them?
不 她是说 只是...
No, she's not saying that It's just...
只是什么?
It's just what?
我们是恋人
We're lovers.
你们俩是一对? 看起来你们不像...
You two are lovers? 'Cause you don't seem...
我们啥不像? 同性恋?
We don't seem what? Gay?
不像 太性感
No. Hot enough.
呃...
Well...
一点都不性感
Not hot at all.
我就知道 不是吗?
I know, right?
装作很忙 精灵点
Look busy, keep your eyes open.
我想我们已经深入野兽的腹中了
I think we're in the belly of the beast.
你是在说我吗?
You talkin' about me?
不
No.
Max 你猜那扇锁着的门后面是什么?
Max, what do you think's behind that locked door?
我就知道! 可怜的俘虏
I knew it! Toddler slaves.
那些孩子冒着成为我的危险
Those kids are in horrible danger of becoming... me.
走吧 我们过去看看
Come on, let's go over there.
你他妈的... 居然敢打我!
What the... you hit me!
对不起 真的 是个意外!
Sorry, so sorry. Accident!
你扔东西就像个娘们一样
You throw like a girl.
看见没 我就知道 你们根本就不是同性恋
See, I knew it, you two aren't gay.
你们就是在勾引我们的男人!
Yous are after our guys!
不 我没有! Rico只是觉得
No, I'm not! Rico just thought I was
我非常 非常 非常漂亮罢了
really, really, really pretty.
噢 不! 放开我的女人!
Oh, hell no! Leave my lover alone!
噢!
Oh!
开战了!
It's on!
不! 不!
No! No!
这不过是... 不 不 不! 还没开始
It's... no, no, no, no, no! It's not on.
太搞笑了 我们才没勾引谁呢
This is silly. We're not after anyone.
我们是来解救那些被...
we're here to help some of those work...
噢 没错 现在 开战吧!
Oh, yeah. Now, it's on!
噢! 我警告你了!
Oh! I warn you!
噢 不!
Oh, hell no!
闪开 婊子!
Back off, bitch!
你叫谁婊子呢 婊子!
Who you calling bitch, bitch?
亲爱的? 你要冷静啊
Honey? You're getting carried away.
现在你可是真的失控了
Now you're really getting carried away.
噢 不! 别把我塞进烘干机!
Oh, no! Don't put me in the dryer!
我以前很有钱的 我只干洗!
I used to be rich, I'm dry clean only!
噢! 噢!
Oh! Oh!
这下你们可闯了大祸了!
That was a big friggin' mistake!
冷静
Respect.
你俩可比天主教学校的女学生
You two are a lot tougher
难对付多了
than those girls from Saint Bridget's.
哇哦 哇哦 发生了什么?
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What's happening?
我们要举报你 我们知道你的勾当了
We're busting you. We know what's happening here.
什么 分享利润和提供医保?
What, profit sharing and healthcare?
我们在盒子里发现了一张纸条写着 "救救我们"
We found a note in our box with "help us" scrawled on it.
你怎么解释?
How do you explain that?
你看了背面了吗?
Did you read the back?
呃 呃
Heh heh heh.
"让我们...
"Help us...
帮助你们...
help you...
在美国王牌发现你的潜力"
to your full potential at American Ace"
我们在每个盒子都会放这么张卡片
We put one in every box we ship.
我必须改一改
I have got to start reading
只看第一句话的毛病了
more than the first sentence of stuff.
对不起 都是我的错
I'm sorry, this is all my fault.
我猜我只是想去相信
I guess I just wanted to believe
有些孩子比我还惨
some kids were having a worse childhood than I was.
Max 别沮丧 你觉得有些人需要帮助
Max, don't feel bad. You thought someone needed help,
你关心他们 这说明你是个好人
and you cared, and that makes you a good person,
我为你骄傲
and I'm proud of you.
我只是说我很抱歉 你没必要这么刻薄吧
I said I was sorry. You don't have to be mean.
嗨 大家好!
Hey, everybody!
我刚收到第一批假发
I just got my first shipment of wigs.
Sophie 你走路怎么是这姿势?
Sophie, why are you walking like that?
因为我不仅仅是老板
Well, I'm not just the president,
我还是客人
I'm also a client.
Sophie 如果这东西不是波斯蟑螂
Sophie, I think you dropped something,
那么我想应该是你的东西
unless we have those giant Persian roaches again.
即使是牛奶版的也是太过了
Even a milky version of that was too much.
Max 或许有一天 有一些像你一样的人
You know, Max, maybe someday, someone like you will come
会来这个充满细菌的餐厅解救我们
into this Salmonella factory and rescue us.
你在支票上写什么呢?
What are you writing on those checks?
"救救我们"
"Help us"
我们在这打工 "救救我们"就是指这里
We work here. The "help us" is implied.